const hiraganaFlashcards = [
  { front: "あ", back: "a" },
  { front: "い", back: "i" },
  { front: "う", back: "u" },
  { front: "え", back: "e" },
  { front: "お", back: "o" },
  { front: "か", back: "ka" },
  { front: "き", back: "ki" },
  { front: "く", back: "ku" },
  { front: "け", back: "ke" },
  { front: "こ", back: "ko" },
  { front: "さ", back: "sa" },
  { front: "し", back: "shi" },
  { front: "す", back: "su" },
  { front: "せ", back: "se" },
  { front: "そ", back: "so" },
  { front: "た", back: "ta" },
  { front: "ち", back: "chi" },
  { front: "つ", back: "tsu" },
  { front: "て", back: "te" },
  { front: "と", back: "to" },
  { front: "な", back: "na" },
  { front: "に", back: "ni" },
  { front: "ぬ", back: "nu" },
  { front: "ね", back: "ne" },
  { front: "の", back: "no" },
  { front: "は", back: "ha" },
  { front: "ひ", back: "hi" },
  { front: "ふ", back: "fu" },
  { front: "へ", back: "he" },
  { front: "ほ", back: "ho" },
  { front: "ま", back: "ma" },
  { front: "み", back: "mi" },
  { front: "む", back: "mu" },
  { front: "め", back: "me" },
  { front: "も", back: "mo" },
  { front: "や", back: "ya" },
  { front: "ゆ", back: "yu" },
  { front: "よ", back: "yo" },
  { front: "ら", back: "ra" },
  { front: "り", back: "ri" },
  { front: "る", back: "ru" },
  { front: "れ", back: "re" },
  { front: "ろ", back: "ro" },
  { front: "わ", back: "wa" },
  { front: "を", back: "wo" },
  { front: "ん", back: "n" },
  { front: "が", back: "ga" },
  { front: "ぎ", back: "gi" },
  { front: "ぐ", back: "gu" },
  { front: "げ", back: "ge" },
  { front: "ご", back: "go" },
  { front: "ざ", back: "za" },
  { front: "じ", back: "ji" },
  { front: "ず", back: "zu" },
  { front: "ぜ", back: "ze" },
  { front: "ぞ", back: "zo" },
  { front: "だ", back: "da" },
  { front: "ぢ", back: "ji" },
  { front: "づ", back: "zu" },
  { front: "で", back: "de" },
  { front: "ど", back: "do" },
  { front: "ば", back: "ba" },
  { front: "び", back: "bi" },
  { front: "ぶ", back: "bu" },
  { front: "べ", back: "be" },
  { front: "ぼ", back: "bo" },
  { front: "ぱ", back: "pa" },
  { front: "ぴ", back: "pi" },
  { front: "ぷ", back: "pu" },
  { front: "ぺ", back: "pe" },
  { front: "ぽ", back: "po" },
  { front: "きゃ", back: "kya" },
  { front: "きゅ", back: "kyu" },
  { front: "きょ", back: "kyo" },
  { front: "しゃ", back: "sha" },
  { front: "しゅ", back: "shu" },
  { front: "しょ", back: "sho" },
  { front: "ちゃ", back: "cha" },
  { front: "ちゅ", back: "chu" },
  { front: "ちょ", back: "cho" },
  { front: "にゃ", back: "nya" },
  { front: "にゅ", back: "nyu" },
  { front: "にょ", back: "nyo" },
  { front: "ひゃ", back: "hya" },
  { front: "ひゅ", back: "hyu" },
  { front: "ひょ", back: "hyo" },
  { front: "みゃ", back: "mya" },
  { front: "みゅ", back: "myu" },
  { front: "みょ", back: "myo" },
  { front: "りゃ", back: "rya" },
  { front: "りゅ", back: "ryu" },
  { front: "りょ", back: "ryo" },
  { front: "ぎゃ", back: "gya" },
  { front: "ぎゅ", back: "gyu" },
  { front: "ぎょ", back: "gyo" },
  { front: "じゃ", back: "ja" },
  { front: "じゅ", back: "ju" },
  { front: "じょ", back: "jo" },
  { front: "びゃ", back: "bya" },
  { front: "びゅ", back: "byu" },
  { front: "びょ", back: "byo" },
  { front: "ぴゃ", back: "pya" },
  { front: "ぴゅ", back: "pyu" },
  { front: "ぴょ", back: "pyo" },
]

const katakanaFlashcards = [
  { front: "ア", back: "a" },
  { front: "イ", back: "i" },
  { front: "ウ", back: "u" },
  { front: "エ", back: "e" },
  { front: "オ", back: "o" },
  { front: "カ", back: "ka" },
  { front: "キ", back: "ki" },
  { front: "ク", back: "ku" },
  { front: "ケ", back: "ke" },
  { front: "コ", back: "ko" },
  { front: "サ", back: "sa" },
  { front: "シ", back: "shi" },
  { front: "ス", back: "su" },
  { front: "セ", back: "se" },
  { front: "ソ", back: "so" },
  { front: "タ", back: "ta" },
  { front: "チ", back: "chi" },
  { front: "ツ", back: "tsu" },
  { front: "テ", back: "te" },
  { front: "ト", back: "to" },
  { front: "ナ", back: "na" },
  { front: "ニ", back: "ni" },
  { front: "ヌ", back: "nu" },
  { front: "ネ", back: "ne" },
  { front: "ノ", back: "no" },
  { front: "ハ", back: "ha" },
  { front: "ヒ", back: "hi" },
  { front: "フ", back: "fu" },
  { front: "ヘ", back: "he" },
  { front: "ホ", back: "ho" },
  { front: "マ", back: "ma" },
  { front: "ミ", back: "mi" },
  { front: "ム", back: "mu" },
  { front: "メ", back: "me" },
  { front: "モ", back: "mo" },
  { front: "ヤ", back: "ya" },
  { front: "ユ", back: "yu" },
  { front: "ヨ", back: "yo" },
  { front: "ラ", back: "ra" },
  { front: "リ", back: "ri" },
  { front: "ル", back: "ru" },
  { front: "レ", back: "re" },
  { front: "ロ", back: "ro" },
  { front: "ワ", back: "wa" },
  { front: "ヲ", back: "wo" },
  { front: "ン", back: "n" },
  { front: "ガ", back: "ga" },
  { front: "ギ", back: "gi" },
  { front: "グ", back: "gu" },
  { front: "ゲ", back: "ge" },
  { front: "ゴ", back: "go" },
  { front: "ザ", back: "za" },
  { front: "ジ", back: "ji" },
  { front: "ズ", back: "zu" },
  { front: "ゼ", back: "ze" },
  { front: "ゾ", back: "zo" },
  { front: "ダ", back: "da" },
  { front: "ヂ", back: "ji" },
  { front: "ヅ", back: "zu" },
  { front: "デ", back: "de" },
  { front: "ド", back: "do" },
  { front: "バ", back: "ba" },
  { front: "ビ", back: "bi" },
  { front: "ブ", back: "bu" },
  { front: "ベ", back: "be" },
  { front: "ボ", back: "bo" },
  { front: "パ", back: "pa" },
  { front: "ピ", back: "pi" },
  { front: "プ", back: "pu" },
  { front: "ペ", back: "pe" },
  { front: "ポ", back: "po" },
  { front: "キャ", back: "kya" },
  { front: "キュ", back: "kyu" },
  { front: "キョ", back: "kyo" },
  { front: "シャ", back: "sha" },
  { front: "シュ", back: "shu" },
  { front: "ショ", back: "sho" },
  { front: "チャ", back: "cha" },
  { front: "チュ", back: "chu" },
  { front: "チョ", back: "cho" },
  { front: "ニャ", back: "nya" },
  { front: "ニュ", back: "nyu" },
  { front: "ニョ", back: "nyo" },
  { front: "ヒャ", back: "hya" },
  { front: "ヒュ", back: "hyu" },
  { front: "ヒョ", back: "hyo" },
  { front: "ミャ", back: "mya" },
  { front: "ミュ", back: "myu" },
  { front: "ミョ", back: "myo" },
  { front: "リャ", back: "rya" },
  { front: "リュ", back: "ryu" },
  { front: "リョ", back: "ryo" },
  { front: "ギャ", back: "gya" },
  { front: "ギュ", back: "gyu" },
  { front: "ギョ", back: "gyo" },
  { front: "ジャ", back: "ja" },
  { front: "ジュ", back: "ju" },
  { front: "ジョ", back: "jo" },
  { front: "ビャ", back: "bya" },
  { front: "ビュ", back: "byu" },
  { front: "ビョ", back: "byo" },
  { front: "ピャ", back: "pya" },
  { front: "ピュ", back: "pyu" },
  { front: "ピョ", back: "pyo" },
]

const koreanHangulFlashcards = [
  // Basic Consonants
  { front: "ㄱ", back: "g/k" },
  { front: "ㄴ", back: "n" },
  { front: "ㄷ", back: "d/t" },
  { front: "ㄹ", back: "r/l" },
  { front: "ㅁ", back: "m" },
  { front: "ㅂ", back: "b/p" },
  { front: "ㅅ", back: "s" },
  { front: "ㅇ", back: "(silent/ng)" },
  { front: "ㅈ", back: "j" },
  { front: "ㅊ", back: "ch" },
  { front: "ㅋ", back: "k" },
  { front: "ㅌ", back: "t" },
  { front: "ㅍ", back: "p" },
  { front: "ㅎ", back: "h" },

  // Double Consonants (Tense Sounds)
  { front: "ㄲ", back: "kk" },
  { front: "ㄸ", back: "tt" },
  { front: "ㅃ", back: "pp" },
  { front: "ㅆ", back: "ss" },
  { front: "ㅉ", back: "jj" },

  // Basic Vowels
  { front: "ㅏ", back: "a" },
  { front: "ㅑ", back: "ya" },
  { front: "ㅓ", back: "eo" },
  { front: "ㅕ", back: "yeo" },
  { front: "ㅗ", back: "o" },
  { front: "ㅛ", back: "yo" },
  { front: "ㅜ", back: "u" },
  { front: "ㅠ", back: "yu" },
  { front: "ㅡ", back: "eu" },
  { front: "ㅣ", back: "i" },

  // Compound Vowels
  { front: "ㅐ", back: "ae" },
  { front: "ㅒ", back: "yae" },
  { front: "ㅔ", back: "e" },
  { front: "ㅖ", back: "ye" },
  { front: "ㅘ", back: "wa" },
  { front: "ㅙ", back: "wae" },
  { front: "ㅚ", back: "oe" },
  { front: "ㅝ", back: "wo" },
  { front: "ㅞ", back: "we" },
  { front: "ㅟ", back: "wi" },
  { front: "ㅢ", back: "ui" },
]

const demoFlashcards = [
  { front: "5 + 3", back: "8" },
  { front: "10 - 4", back: "6" },
  { front: "7 × 2", back: "14" },
  { front: "9 ÷ 3", back: "3" },
  { front: "Square root of 16", back: "4" },
  { front: "12 ÷ 4", back: "3" },
  { front: "15 + 5", back: "20" },
  { front: "100 ÷ 10", back: "10" },
  { front: "9 × 9", back: "81" },
  { front: "20 - 15", back: "5" },
]

export const decksForSignups = [
  {
    name: "Japanese Hiragana",
    pathname: "japanese-hiragana",
    _cards: hiraganaFlashcards,
  },
  {
    name: "Japanese Katakana",
    pathname: "japanese-katakana",
    _cards: katakanaFlashcards,
  },
  {
    name: "Korean Hangul Alphabet",
    pathname: "korean-hangul-alphabet",
    _cards: koreanHangulFlashcards,
  },
  {
    name: "Demo",
    description:
      "Demo deck to quickly preview the functionality. It only has 4 levels and the timings for the spaced repetition system are 30 seconds, 1 minute and 5 minutes.",
    pathname: "demo",
    srsTimingsType: "demo",
    _cards: demoFlashcards,
  },
]
